珍，希望这不会让你感到尴尬
但我发现评估新员工最好的方式
就是以严厉的目光凝视他们
— 所以！
— 所以
— 第一天！
— 对！
— 感到害怕？
— 是的……
— 不要害怕！
— 我其实没有害怕
你应该会感到害怕
— 嗯我是有那么一点点害怕
— 啊？别怕！
你说了算吧！
一定期待已久了吧！
是
我…… 非常期待……
— 可以开始了解……
— 我准备把你放到IT部门
因为你在简历里说你对计算机有很丰富的经验
我在我的简历中是有提到，确实。
我对整个计算机领域有着……
非常丰富的经验…… 你知道的，电子邮件……
发送邮件，接受邮件,
删除邮件...
– 我还能继续说下去
– 说下去！
万维网…… 使用鼠……
鼠标…… 用鼠标
单击…… 双击……
当然还有屏幕，键盘
那个放在地下的小东西……
— 硬盘？
— 对的
看来，你确实对你的工作十分了解
没别的问题了
我看好你，珍！
而且他们需要一个新的主管
太好了！
所以…… 那些将和我一起工作的人，
都怎么样呢？
标准的书呆子！
你好，I.T.
你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
好，那么，侧面的按钮，是亮着的吗？
嗯，你需要把它打开！
那个按钮，把它打开？！
嗯…… 你…… 嗯……
你不会连怎么按按钮都不知道吧？
不，不是在衣服上的！
你好，I.T.？
Yeah?
你是否尝试过意外强制重启？
不不不！可以了！不，已经可以了，
我刚听到它启动了
不不不，那是它启动的声音
不是，那是它启动的……
对不起，你是从古代来的吗？
看起来是驱动程序通过修改系统调用表来挂钩函数
而这时重载它是不安全的
除非另一个线程正要插入那里
并执行它自己的任务
你也不想最终进入无效内存里面吧
你好？
Really? Really, why don't you come
down here and make me then?
What? Oh you think I'm afraid of you?
I'm not afraid of you!
You can come down here any time
and I'll be waiting for ya!
That told her!
Oh God, it's about time you got back,
it's been all go.
You had a job?
Girl on fifth...
你和她…… 一拍即合了吗？
Did you and her... hit it off?
定义“一拍即合”？
Define "hit it off"?
她在你修好她的电脑之后继续和你聊天吗？
Did she continue talking to you
once you'd fixed her computer?
没有……
No...
而且在我修她的电脑的时候，她把一个杯子放在我背上
And while I was working on it,
she rested a cup on my back.
— 不是吧？！
– No?!
—— 是的！
– Yep!
难以置信！
Unbelievable!
是的，他们对我们一点都不尊重，一点也没有！
Yeah, I mean they've not respect for us
up there, no respect whatsoever!
我们对他们来说只是干苦力的
We're all just drudgens to them.
对！
Yes!
如果有这么一个词叫“干苦力”
If there were such a thing as a drudgen,
那就是我们对他们的意义
that is what we'd be to them.
每当他们的打印机出问题的时候
It's like they're pally-wally
他们就像好朋友一样
when there's a problem
with their printer
但一旦问题解决了……
but once it's fixed...
他们就把我们抛在一边，就像隔夜的果酱一样！
They toss us away like yesterday's jam!
对！
Yes!
隔夜的果酱！
Yesterday's jam!
这就是我们对他们的意义！
That is what we are to them!
其实你知道吗？
Actually you know what?
这个说法并不太恰当……
That doesn't really work as a thing...
因为你知道的，果酱可以保存很久……
because you know, jam lasts for ages...
你好，I.T.？
Hello, I.T. ?
你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
中性厕所？你们有中性厕所，就像《艾莉的异想世界》里面那样？
Unisex toilets? You have unisex toilets,
like Ally McBeal?
这就是这个地方的情况，珍
That's the sort of place this is, Jen.
很多性感的人，不怎么工作…… 还有一些婚外情
A lot of sexy people not doing
much work... and having affairs.
哦我的天啊！看那景色！
Oh my God! Look at that view!
我感觉我仿佛站在世界之巅
I feel like I'm on top of the world.
好了，珍，我就送你到这里了
Well Jen, this is where I leave you.
34层
Floor 34.
好的，谢谢你
Great sir, thank you.
嗯，我要该哪里？
OK. Where am I going?
一路…… 下到地下室
All... the way down to the basement.
祝你好运！
Good luck!
离开电梯……
Get out of the lift...
— 哦，不好意思，我马上就好！
– Oh. Won't be a tick!
— 哦我的天啊！
– Oh my God!
哦我的天啊！哦天啊！好吧
Oh my God! Oh God! OK.
有人吗？
Hello?
是的，我相信是托尔斯泰说过……
Yes I believe it was Tolstoy who said...
噢，看来我们有客人了
Oh, it seems we have a visitor.
抱歉，我和莫里斯刚刚在
I'm sorry, myself and Morris
were just engaged
认真讨论书籍之类的事情
in quite a serious discussion
about books and such.
我们没听到你进来
We didn't hear you come in.
等会，你说是托尔斯泰说的，他说了什么？
Wait a second, you said it was
Tolstoy, he said what?
噢别在意那个，莫里斯！
Oh never mind that now, Morris!
你什么时候读过托尔斯泰？
When have you read Tolstoy?
闭嘴，莫里斯！
Shut up, Morris!
你为什么用那种奇怪的声音说话？
Why are you speaking that weird voice?
什么时候有…… 我完全不记得这段对话
When did... I don't remember
this conversation at all!
Don't... don't let me disturb you,
I just wanted to come down....
Don't be silly you never dist...
很多人下来拜访！
Many people come down here to visit!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
谁下来？什么人？
Who comes down? What people?
你为什么要给我秘密信号让我闭嘴？
Why are you giving me
the secret signal to shut up?!
所以…… 我们有什么可以到帮你？
So... What can we do you for?
我是这个部门的新主管
I'm the new head of this department.
这是我的办公室吗？
Is this my office?
为什么？她说了什么…… 她刚刚说……
Why? What did she... Did she just say...
— 我是这个部门的新主管！
– I am the head of this department!
— 我觉得我是
–  I thought I was.
是我们中的一个！反正不是她！
It's one of us! Certainly not her!
我要去解决这个问题……
I'm gonna sort this out...
罗伊！你头上有伤口……
Roy! You've got a head wound there...
头上有伤口！
Head wound!
嗨！
Hi!
我不想变得无礼或者怎么样
I don't wanna be rude or anything
但是我没有收到任何关于这个部门的变动的通知
but I wasn't informed of any changes
to this department.
噢，他们没有告诉你关于我的事吗？
Oh, did they not tell you about me?
没有！
No!
And we are perfectly fine down here,
thank you very much,
we're more than capable
of taking care of ourselves.
好…… 好……
Sure... sure...
你知道你满头都是血吗？
You know you're covered in blood?
莫斯！
Moss!
Amazon thingy.
Wicked!
我知道这是什么
I know what this is.
这是新的哈利波特
It's the new Harry Potter.
我买了儿童版和成人版
I got the child edition
and the adult edition
只是为了检查一下，看看有没有不同的地方
just to check that there are
no differences in the text.
对不起但是我不会和那个女人打交道！
Sorry but I'm not gonna be able
to deal with that woman!
Is nobody else going to get the phone?
I suppose I'll get it!
No, that is not a phone.
I'm gonna have a little lie down.
进来！
Come in!
是的，丹农。是的，是的
Yeah, Denholm. Yeah, yeah.
不不不…… 不，到目前为止都还好
No no no... No they've been fine so far.
是的。我觉得我们会相处得很好
Yeah. I think we're gonna get on great.
好的，我知道
Yeah, I know.
好的，那么，你保重
All right then, now you take care.
好的，是我会的，是的
All right, yeah I will, yeah.
好！
Ok!
好了，保重，保重！
Ok, take care, take care!
好了，拜拜！拜拜！
Ok bye! Bye!
噢，所以，你好！
Oh, so, hello!
你需要我……
What can I do you fo...
我能为你做什么？
What can I do for you?
你好，我只是在想……
Hello. I was just wondering...
你需要我帮你接通电话吗？
Do you want me to connect up your phone?
不不不…… 不
No no no... No.
它在工作
It's working.
我才和丹农聊过
I was just talking to Denholm.
但，怎么？！
But how?!
Oh do you mind... Do you mind
closing the door for me?
— 噢，是的，当然
– Oh yeah, sure.
— 是，好的
– Yeah, Ok.
对。从另一边……
Yeah. From the other side...
当然
Of course.
— 像这样？
– Like this?
— 就是这样！
– That's it!
—
– With me on the...
— 谢谢！
– Thanks!
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
噢是的，莫斯，我没事！
Oh yes, Moss, I'm fine!
护士说我没有对自己造成严重的伤害
The nurse said I didn't do myself
any serious damage.
我站在这边呢！
I'm standing over here!
我知道，我知道，我在开玩笑，我没事！
I know, I know, I'm joking, I'm fine!
What we gonna do about her?
额，我刚刚进去，她在假装和人聊天
Well, I just went in, and she was having
a pretend conversation.
— 真的？
– Really?
— 是的
– Yes.
她有点奇怪…… 至少可以这么说
She's a little bit weird...
to say the least.
这是什么？
What's that?
噢，只是水
Oh just water.
有时候，我会觉得耳朵变得很热
Sometimes, I get a hot ear,
而这样可以让他冷却下来
and this helps cool it down.
她真是个怪人……
She is quite the oddbod...
你注意到了吗？
Did you notice how
她居然没有感觉到兴奋
she didn't even get excited
当她看到这个原版的ZX-IT 1的时候？
when she saw this original ZX-IT 1?
是的，那真是奇怪
Yeah, that was weird.
几乎就像她对计算机一无所知
It's almost as if she doesn't know
anything about computers.
什么？！
What?!
看看你干了什么！
Look what you did!
噢别担心，这就是为什么
Oh don't worry that's why
我总是泡两杯茶
I always make 2 cups of tea.
不管怎么说，我们在说什么？
Anyway, what were we talking about?
噢，她对计算机一无所知
Oh, her not knowing anything
about computers.
什么？！
What?!
I definitely want to get rid of her.
I agree yeah.
好，所以，这是计划：
Ok, so, here's the plan:
一个计划？让我戴上我的稍大一点的眼镜
A plan? Let me put on
my slightly larger glasses.
好，说吧！
Ok, hit me!
— 好，我们进去……
– Ok. We go in...
— 什么时候？
– When?
你知道，差不多就在一分钟之后
You know, like in a minute.
会有足够的时间让我了解这个计划吗？
Will that be enough time for me
to get to know the plan?
是的，你知道吗？
Yeah, you know what?
我不该用“计划”这个词！
I shouldn't have used the word "plan"!
我…… 我显然让你激动过头了！
I... I've clearly gotten you
over-excited!
“想法”会不会是更好一点的词？
Would "steamed" be a better word?
虽然这也很激动人心，
Although that's just as exciting,
但是我可能会用这个词
I might even use these.
我只是想说……
All I was gonna say was...
我们进去，我编造一堆关于计算机的废话
We go in, I make up a load of bullocks
about computers
然后我们看看她会不会察觉到
and we'll see if she picks up on it.
是的，我明白为什么你不想用“计划”这个词了
Yes. I can see why
you didn't want to use the word "plan".
让我来说
Let me do the talk.
好的
All right.
Ouh, Moss, Moss Moss!
好的，我们一定要要把这个定，你知道吗？
Ok, we need to get this right, you know?
我们…… 我们需要保持冷静
We... we need to stay calm.
我们不想半途而废
We do not wanna go in there half-cocked.
等一下，伙计们
Hang on, guys.
我能帮忙吗？
How can I help?
我们刚才在想
Well, we were just wondering
既然现在你是“老板”了
now that you're "The Boss",
你想让我们接入数据供应商
would you like us to access
the data supplier
然后把你连接到矩阵里面？
and connect you up to the matrix?
你刚才说的全是胡扯吧？
You just made all that up?
你对计算机一无所知，承认吧！
You don't know anything
about computers, admit it!
Will you stop trying to undermine me!
Now get in there,
and do some work, to do with computers!
I'll be in there in a minute
and check up on you!
听着，小姐！
Ok, lady!
你虽然赢了这一回，但是我们会等着你！
You've won this round, but we can wait!
你总有一天会露馅的，
You will slip up one day,
and believe you me,
we will be there when you do!
There will be some piece of evidence
that will prove
without any shadow of a doubt
that you don't know
anything about computers.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
帮你的电脑插上电源
Plugging in your computer.
It might be something you say...
or something you do!
But when we notice this,
and believe me we will notice this,
there's gonna be a long way down
for you, sweet chicks!
他很快就会意识到的……
He'll realize in a second...
我真的你们要告发我
I cannot believe you're going
to tell on me.
你们就像一对可怕的老太太
You're like a pair of horrible
old women.
她刚才说了什么？
What did she say?
她说我们就像一对可怕的老太太
She said we're like horrible old women.
She didn't!
嘿，伙计们！
Hey guys!
好，有事情要告诉我？
Ok, got something to tell me?
Yes, well, it's like this:
看看你们！我的I.T.团队
Look at you! My I.T. Team.
— 是的
– Yeah.
— 你们每个人都是团队的一员
– Team players each and every one of you.
是的，
Yeah, what she...
这里没有空间留给那些在我的团队里不能做好团队合作的人
There's no room for people
who can't act in a team on my team!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你好？
Hello?
什么？！
What?!
Well if you can't work as a team,
you're all fired!
好，你听到我说的，好！
That's it, you heard me, fine!
拿着你的东西走人！
Get your things and go!
你好，安保？
Hello, Security?
四楼的所有人都被开除了
Everyone on floor 4 is fired.
请把他们从那个地方赶出去
Escort them from the premises.
并且要团队合作！
And do it as a team!
记住你们是一个团队，如果你们不能
Remember you're a team, and if you can't
做到团队合作，你们也会被开除！
act as a team, you're fired too!
该死的！
Dawn!
接到招聘部门
Get onto recruitment.
告诉他们找一个安保团队
Tell them to look for a security team
能够团队合作的
that can work as team.
他们可能要把我们的安保团队
They may have to escort our
从这栋大楼里面赶出去
security team from the building,
因为他们没有团队合作的精神！
for not acting like a team!
团队！团队 团队 团队 团队！
Team! Team team team team team!
我非常喜欢“团队”这个词
I even love saying the word "team".
你们也许会认为这是我家人的照片？
You probably think that's a picture
of my family?
这是A级团队
It's the A-Team.
波蒂亚，多伊尔，老虎，珠宝人！
Body, Doyle, Tiger, the Jewellery Man!
他们都是我的团队！
All of them!
所以你们想告诉我什么？
So what do you wanna tell me?
嗯，我们相处得就是不太好
Well, it's just not working out.
— 他在开玩笑！
– He's joking!
— 但是你说……
– But you said...
不太好？
Not working out?
噢不！没有！
Oh no! No!
我们相处得非常非常好！
We are getting on like
a big house on fire!
— 是的！
– Yeah!
— 我的耳朵越来越热了！
– My ear's getting hot!
不是…… 你知道吗？
No... You know what?
我们应该走了，现在，因为
We should leave, now, because
你也知道，你很忙
you know, you're a busy man
而我们占用了太多你的时间
and we've taken far too much
of your time.
珍，你可以帮我把门打开吗？
Jen could you just get the door
for me there?
当然啦，罗伊！
Absolutely Roy!
所以为什么你们一开始就来这里？
So why did you come here
in the first place?
我们为您的电脑设置了一个语音激活系统
We set up a voice activation system
on your computer.
我觉得你会喜欢上它的
I think you're gonna enjoy it.
只不过它可能需要一点时间来适应你的声音
It might just take a little while
to get the pitch right on the voice
但是不管怎样，试试看吧！
but nonetheless, go ahead!
非常感谢你们！
Thank you very much!
— 拜拜！
– Bye bye!
— 谢谢你们！
– Thank you!
真兴奋啊！
How exciting!
你好……
Hello...
你好，电脑！
Hello computer!
你好！
Hello!
你好…… 你好，电脑……
Hello... Hello computer...
你是什么东西啊？
What good are you?
你
You obviously don't know anything
about computers.
No but... OK.
But I can learn.
You know, I mean, for example Moss,
you could take me through
what you're doing right now.
I'd be delighted!
I'm just working on a very simple piece
of programming code.
I see...
Oh God, no, I'm lying again!
I didn't understand any of that!
I don't know anything
about computers, I mean...
I'm absolutely useless to you.
I might as well pack up and go home.
Hi! Is... Roy around?
Hello there little lady!
Are you lost?
How can I help you? I'm Roy.
You wanted me to come down?!
Well here I am!!
Not the face!!
Well maybe this will teach you
to treat people with
a little bit of respect!
Is it 'cos we spoke on the phone
earlier?
Oh my God! Are those Manolo's?
Yes!
They are gorgeous! Were they expensive?
No! Got them in a sale.
Oh God! Clever you!
I'm never lucky enough
to get a bargain myself.
Well, I should take you shopping.
Yeah, no that would be fantastic.
Oh I will give you a call.
Nice to meet you! Take care!
– Nice meeting you!
– Chairman! Wow!
You just diffuse that entire situation!
What situation?
Oh, that.. yeah!
Oh my God, does that happen a lot?
They're fairly regular,
the beatings, yes.
I'd say we're on a by-weekly beatings.
Ah it's not all that bad!
Ah, come on Roy! It's pretty bad...
Maybe I could help with this.
You know, I mean...
I'm a people person and...
people like you need a person
to deal with people...
a people person like me. Oh my God!
Ideas are coming!
Things are happening here!
Ok, Ok, what would you say here,
if I told you that I had a plan
to raise your profile upstairs by 100%.
What would you say?
I can't be done! You're crazy!
What would you say Roy?
Roy's passed out! Ok!
我需要一只毛毡笔，还有一些纸
I need a felt-tip pen, and some paper.
派对 - I.T.部门 今天 5:45
PARTY - I.T. DEPT 5.45 TODAY
不不！噢不，真的真的真的，
No no! Oh no, really really really,
那是一个真实的故事！
that was a true story!
难以置信！
Unbelievable!
我就说为什么我们不经常和I.T.部门的人一起出去？
I said why we don't go out
with the I.T. guys more often?
— 你们太搞笑了！
– You're hilarious!
— 是的，我们是！
– Yes we are!
你们应该经常来这里的
You guys should come down here
more often you know,
你应该把这看作是雷南公司的一个新时代
you should see this as a new era
for Reynholm Industries.
“雷南公司的新时代！”
"A new era for Reynholm Industries!"
你知道吗！如果你想听一个真的很有趣的故事
Do you know what! If you want
to hear something really funny,
一个真的很有趣的故事
a really funny story,
你们应该听听我和莫斯在阿姆斯特丹的时候发生的事
you should hear what happened
to Moss and I,
我们喝得醉醺醺的时候
when we were so drunk in Amsterdam
然后莫斯丢了他的眼镜！
that Moss lost his glasses!
莫斯！莫斯！
Moss! Moss!
过来！过来！
Come here! Come here!
告诉他们我们在阿姆斯特丹喝醉的时候发生的事
Tell them that story about
when we were drunk in Amsterdam.
真的吗？
Really?
是啊是啊是啊！哦这个故事太棒了！
Yeah yeah yeah! Oh it's brilliant!
噢这个故事太棒了，
Oh this a great story,
你们一定会喜欢的！
you're gonna love it!
我要再拿一盒红酒！
I'm just gonna get another box of wine!
很好，继续
Well go on, then.
好的
All right.
— 嗯，有一天，我们喝得很醉
– Well, one night, we were really drunk.
— 是的
– Yeah.
然后呢，我们实在是太醉了，就决定去找妓女
And huh, we were so drunk
that we decided to hire prostitutes.
然而当她们到了酒店，
And when they arrived to the hotel,
我们实在太害怕了，什么都不敢做，
we were too scared to do anything,
所以我们带她们去了游乐场
so we brought them to the fair.
噢真的很棒！最后，
Oh really nice! In the end,
他们只收了我们一半的钱
they only charged us half.
但是我们还是要为所有的游乐项目付钱
But we did have to pay
for all the rides.
噢难道这不是最棒的故事吗？
Oh isn't that just the best story?
哦各位！
Oh, man!
你告诉过我不要把这件事告诉任何人
You told me to never tell that story
to anyone.
啊，你在说什么呢？
Well, what're you talking about?
这是一个绝妙的故事！
That's a brilliant story!
后来你几乎要走到水沟里去
And then you nearly walked
into the canal!
Has it got to that part
with the boatman?
你说的是我丢了我的眼镜的那个故事吗？
Do you mean the story
when I lost my glasses?
对啊！
Yes!
你觉得我说的是什么故事？
What story did you think I mean?
莫斯？
Moss?
你说了什么？！你说了什么？！
What did you say?! What did you say?!
这就很适合你们两个
It's all right for you two.
You're used to being social social piranhas...
我一般是个很受欢迎的人
I'm a very popular person usually.
之前那个，想用她的鞋子把我打死的女孩
That girl earlier, that tried
to beat me to death with her shoes,
有人有她的电话号码吗？
did anybody get her number?
讲道理这真是美好的一天，不是吗？
That was a nice day the fair, wasn't it?
With Brandy and Crystal!
你好，I.T.？
Hello I.T.?
嗯，你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
Yeah. Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
你好！你好！
Hello! Hello!